<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?NLS TYPE="org.eclipse.help.contexts"?>
<!-- /*******************************************************************************
 * Copyright (c) 2000, 2006 IBM Corporation and others.
 * All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials
 * are made available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License v1.0
 * which accompanies this distribution, and is available at
 * http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v10.html
 * 
 * Contributors:
 *     IBM Corporation - initial API and implementation
 *******************************************************************************/ -->
<contexts>

<!--DRES: Resource Selection Dialog-->
<context id="DRES0001">
<!--Resource Type drop down-->
<description>Select a resource from which to create a Web service.</description>
</context>
<context id="DRES0002">
<!--Resource tree-->
<description>Lists the resources that can be turned into a Web service.</description>
</context>

<!--PPRM: Resource Management Preference page-->

<context id="PPRM0001">
<!--main page-->
<description>The Resource Management preferences enable you to determine the defaults that you want to use when creating your Web service.</description>
</context>

<context id="PPRM0002">
<!--File overwrite check box-->
<description>This checkbox allows you to overwrite files without receiving a warning message asking for confirmation when overwriting files.</description>
</context>
<context id="PPRM0003">
<!--Create folders check box-->
<description>Select this checkbox to create folders and folder structures without receiving a warning message asking for confirmation.</description>
</context>
<context id="PPRM0004">
<!--Check out files check box-->
<description>Select this checkbox to check out files without receiving a warning message asking for confirmation.</description>
</context>

<context id="PPRM0005">
<!--Skeleton merge-->
<description>This check box is disabled by default. If this check box is enabled, when a skeleton 
file of the same name already exists in the workspace, the newly generated skeleton file will merge 
with the existing skeleton file.  Enable this to preserve code that you have already modified in the 
existing skeleton files.  
</ br>
Note that when this preference is enabled, if you change the return type
of an interface, the resulting skeleton file will have a method returning the
type as defined in the new interface but would have a method body from the
original skeleton file (which would be returning a different type).  This will
result in an compilation error that the you will have to correct manually.

</description>
</context>

<!--PPSD: Scenario Defaults Preference page-->

<!--ScenarioDefaultsPreferencePage.java-->
<context id="PPSD0001">
<!--PPSD0001 for the Scenario Defaults Preference Page-->
<description>Use this page to select the default settings for the Web services wizard.</description>
</context>
<context id="PPSD0002">
<!--PPSD0002 for the launch sample check box on the Scenario Defaults Preference Page-->
<description>The Scenario Defaults preferences enable you to determine the defaults that you want to use when creating your Web service. The sample Web application demonstrates how to code the proxy file. Select this check box to launch sample application after it is created.</description>
</context>
<context id="PPSD0004">
<!--PPSD0004 for the sample JSP type combo box on the Scenario Defaults Preference Page-->
<description>Select the type of sample JSP to be created.</description>
</context>
<context id="PPSD0003">
<!--PPSD0003 for the web explorer type combo box on the Scenario Defaults Preference Page-->
<description>The Scenario Defaults preferences enable you to determine the defaults that you want to use when creating your Web service. Select from the available Web services explorers.</description>
</context>
<context id="PPSD0005">
<!--PPSD0005 for the User-defined UDDI Category Data Column Delimiter text field on the Scenario Defaults Preference Page-->
<description>Enter the character you want to use as a column delimiter for user-defined UDDI Category data.</description>
</context>
<context id="PPSD0006">
<!--PPSD0006 for the User-defined UDDI Category Data String Delimiter text field on the Scenario Defaults Preference Page-->
<description>Enter the character you want to use as a string delimiter for user-defined UDDI Category data.</description>
</context>


<context id="PPAD0004">
<!--  Hide generate client check box-->
<description>Select this check box to hide the option of generating a Web service client when you right-click a file in the Project Explorer or Navigator.</description>
</context>

<context id="PPAD0005">
<!--  Hide generate sample check box-->
<description>Select this check box to hide the option of generating sample JSP code for the Web service when you right-click a file in the Project Explorer or Navigator.</description>
</context>

<context id="PPAD0006">
<!--  create web service check box-->
<description>Select this check box to hide the option of generating a Web service client when you right-click a file in the Project Explorer or Navigator.</description>
</context>

<context id="PPAD0008">
<!--  generate skeleton check box-->
<description>Select this check box to hide the option of generating skeleton Java classes when you right-click a file in the Project Explorer or Navigator. The skeleton bean contains a set of methods that correspond to the operations described in the WSDL document. When the bean is created, each method has a trivial implementation that you replace by editing the bean.</description>
</context>

<context id="PPAD0009">
<!--  publish WSDL check box-->
<description>Select this check box to hide the option of publishing the Web service's WSDL file to a UDDI registry when you right-click a file in the Project Explorer or Navigator.</description>
</context>


</contexts>