<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?NLS TYPE="org.eclipse.help.contexts"?>
<!-- /*******************************************************************************
 * Copyright (c) 2000, 2006 IBM Corporation and others.
 * All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials
 * are made available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License v1.0
 * which accompanies this distribution, and is available at
 * http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v10.html
 * 
 * Contributors:
 *     IBM Corporation - initial API and implementation
 *******************************************************************************/ -->
<contexts>

<!--WebServiceAxisProxyPage.java-->

<context id="PWJB0001">
<!--WSDL to Java Bindings Page-->
<description>Select the location where the Web service client will be created. The Java bean client proxy that is generated provides a remote procedure call interface to the Web service.</description>
</context>

<context id="PWJB0003">
<!--Folder field of the WSDL to Java Bindings Page-->
<description>Select the project and folder in which the Web service client will be created.</description>
</context>

<context id="PWJB0009">
<!--Indicates whether to generate a proxy or not-->
<description>Select this check box Java bean client proxy to the Web service. The Java bean client proxy that is generated provides a remote procedure call interface to the Web service.</description>
</context>

<context id="PWJB0016">
<!--Show Mappings checkbox of the Bean Methods Page-->
<description>Select this check box to customize the mappings between packages and namespaces.</description>
</context>

<!--WebServiceAxisMappingsPage.java-->

<context id="PWJM0001">
<!--WSDL to Java Mappings Page-->
<description>Use this panel to add customized package to namespace mappings.</description>
</context>

<!--AxisEmitterPreferencePage.java-->

<context id="PPAE0001">
<!--Axis Emitter Preference Page-->
<description>Use this page to select the default behavior of the wizards when generating Axis Web services.</description>
</context>

<context id="PPAE0002">
<!--Generate code for all elements-->
<description>By default, WSDL2Java only generates code for those elements in the WSDL file that are referenced. Selecting this checkbox will generate code for all elements in the scope regardless of whether they are referenced. By default, the scope is all WSDL files; if generateImports(false), then the scope is only the immediate WSDL file.</description>
</context>

<context id="PPAE0003">
<!--Emits separate Helper classes for metadata-->
<description>If you select this option WSDL2Java will create a separate helper class that contains the metadata rather than including it in the skeleton.</description>
</context>

<context id="PPAE0004">
<!--Prefers building beans to straight arrays for wrapped XML array types-->
<description>If you would rather a specific JavaBean class (ArrayOfString) be generated for these types of schemas, select this option.</description>
</context>

<context id="PPAE0005">
<!--Add scope to deploy.wsdd-->
<description>This indicates how to deploy the server implementation. 
Application uses one instance of the implementation class for all requests. 
Request creates a new instance of the implementation class for each request. 
Session creates a new instance of the implementation class for each session.</description>
</context>

<context id="PPAE0006">
<!--Timeout-->
<description>The default is 45 seconds. Use -1 to disable the timeout.</description>
</context>

<context id="PPAE0007">
<!--Look for allowed methods in inherited class-->
<description>If this option is specified, the Java2WSDL parser will look into extended classes to determine the list of methods to export into the WSDL file.</description>
</context>

<context id="PPAE0008">
<!--Look for allowed methods in inherited class-->
<description>Use this page to select the default behavior of the wizards when generating Axis Web services.</description>
</context>

<context id="PPAE0009">
<!--Look for allowed methods in inherited class-->
<description>Use this page to select the default behavior of the wizards when generating Axis Web services.</description>
</context>

<context id="PPAE0010">
<!--validate against JAXRPC-->
<description>If selected, the tools will examine the Java service class and its value types to determine if it satisfies important requirements of the JAX-RPC specification.</description>
</context>

</contexts>
