<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?NLS TYPE="org.eclipse.help.contexts"?>
<!-- /*******************************************************************************
 * Copyright (c) 2000, 2006 IBM Corporation and others.
 * All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials
 * are made available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License v1.0
 * which accompanies this distribution, and is available at
 * http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v10.html
 * 
 * Contributors:
 *     IBM Corporation - initial API and implementation
 *******************************************************************************/ -->
<contexts>

<context id="PWRS0002">
<!--  Run-time/servers in the Web Service type-->
<description>Select the scenario configuration for run-time environments, servers, and projects.</description>
</context>

<context id="PWPR0001">
<!-- Project Page -->
<description>Select the type of Web service you want to generate and any file and folder options for your Web service.</description>
</context>

<context id="PWPR0005">
<!--  Generate Proxy check box of the Project Page -->
<description>The generated Java bean proxy provides a remote procedure call interface to the Web service.</description>
</context>

<context id="PWPR0009">
<!--  Start Web Project check box check box of the Project Page -->
<description>Click to start the server. If you leave the box unchecked you will have to manually start the server.</description>
</context>

<context id="PWPR0010">
<!-- Web Service Type combo box of the Project Page -->
<description>Select the type of Web service you want to build. Your selection will affect the files available for selection.</description>
</context>

<context id="PWPR0011">
<!--  Wizard Scenario Service group of the Project Page -->
<description>Select the type of Web service you want to build. Your selection will affect the files available for selection.</description>
</context>

<context id="PWPR0013">
<!--  Test service checkbox of the project page -->
<description>Select this check box to launch the Web service in the Web Services Explorer in order to examine it.</description>
</context>

<context id="PWPR0012">
<!--  Launch UDDI check box of the Project Page -->
<description>Select this checkbox to launch the Web Services Explorer in order to publish the Web service to a UDDI registry.</description>
</context>

<context id="PWPR0014">
<!--  Web Service Client Type combo box of the Project Page -->
<description>Select the client proxy type. The generated Java bean proxy provides a remote procedure call interface to the Web service.</description>
</context>



<context id="PSTP0001">
<!--  Test Type Combo box of the Service Test Page-->
<description>Select the test facility in which you would like to test the Web service being created.</description>
</context>

<context id="PSTP0002">
<!--  Launch button of the Service Test Page-->
<description>Click this to launch the Web service in a browser window to test it.</description>
</context>

<!--WebServiceWizNewFirstPage-->

<context id="WSWSCEN0001">
<!-- First Page-->
<description>On this page select the artifact from which your Web service or client will be created, and the stages of Web services development that you want
to complete:
<ul>
<li>Develop: this will create the service code</li>
<li>Assemble: this ensures that the project that will host the Web service or 
client gets associated to an EAR when required by the target application server</li>
<li>Deploy: this will create the deployment code for the service</li>
<li>Install: this will install the service on the chosen server</li>
<li>Start: this will start the server once the service has been installed on it</li>
<li>Test: this will provide various options for testing the service</li>
</ul>
Select the server and runtime for your Web service or client, and whether or not you want to publish or monitor the service.
</description>
</context>

<context id="WSWSCEN0010">
<!--Web service type combo box of the First Page-->
<description>Select the type of Web service you want to create. A bottom-up service creates a service from a Java bean or EJB, while a top-down service will create 
a service from a WSDL file and then create a skeleton Java bean or EJB for you to implement later.</description>
</context>

<context id="WSWSCEN0014">
<!--Monitor checkbox of the First Page-->
<description>Monitor the Web service: this will send the Web service traffic
through the TCP/IP Monitor, which allows you to watch the SOAP traffic generated
by the Web service and to test this traffic for WS-I compliance.</description>
</context>

<context id="WSWSCEN0012">
<!--Launch UDDI check box of the First Page-->
<description>Publish the Web service: this will launch the Web Services Explorer
to publish your Web service to a UDDI registry.</description>
</context>

<context id="WSWSCEN0020">
<!--Service implementation field of the First Page-->
<description>Enter the URI to the WSDL, WSIL, or HTML file that
will be used to generate the service</description>
</context>

<context id="WSWSCEN0021">
<!--Service slider of the First Page-->
<description>Select the stages of Web services development that you want
to complete using the slider:
<ul>
<li>Develop: this will create the service code</li>
<li>Assemble: </li>
<li>Deploy: this will create the deployment code for the service</li>
<li>Install: this will install the service on the chosen server</li>
<li>Start: this will start the server once the service has been installed on it</li>
<li>Test: this will provide various options for testing the service</li>
</ul></description>
</context>

<context id="WSWSCEN0022">
<!--Server link of the First Page-->
<description>Select your server: the default server is displayed. If you
want to deploy your service to a different server click the link to specify
a different server.</description>
</context>

<context id="WSWSCEN0023">
<!--runtime link of the First Page-->
<description>Select your runtime: the default runtime is displayed. If you
want to deploy your service to a different runtime click the link to specify
a different runtime.</description>
</context>

<context id="WSWSCEN0024">
<!--projects link of the First Page-->
<description>Select the service project: the project containing the project
selected in your workspace is displayed. To select a different project and
EAR click on the project link. Ensure that the project selected
as the Client Web Project is different from the Service Web Project, or the
service will be overwritten by the client's generated artifacts.</description>
</context>

<context id="WSWSCEN0025">
<!--client type combo of the First Page-->
<description>The Java bean client proxy that is generated provides a remote procedure call interface to the Web service.</description>
</context>

<context id="WSWSCEN0026">
<!--Client slider of the First Page-->
<description>Select the stages of Web services client development that you want
to complete using the slider:
<ul>
<li>Develop: this will create the client code</li>
<li>Assemble: </li>
<li>Deploy: this will create the deployment code for the client</li>
<li>Install: this will install the client on the chosen server</li>
<li>Start: this will start the server once the client has been installed on it</li>
<li>Test: this will provide various options for testing the client</li>
</ul></description>
</context>

<context id="WSWSCEN0030">
<!--file overwrite checkbox of the First Page-->
<description>This allows you to overwrite files without receiving a warning message asking for confirmation when overwriting files.</description>
</context>

</contexts>
