<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    Copyright (c) 2009, 2019 Shane Clarke.
    This program and the accompanying materials
    are made available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License 2.0
    which accompanies this distribution, and is available at
    https://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-2.0/

    SPDX-License-Identifier: EPL-2.0

    Contributors:
        Shane Clarke - initial API and implementation
 -->

<cheatsheet title="Create a project for CXF Web services">
   <intro
         href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/reference/ref-cheatsheets.htm">
      <description>
            This cheat sheet will demonstrate how to create a Dynamic Web Project and enable it for CXF JAX-WS Web service development.
            <br/>
            <br/>
If you need help at any step, click the help button in the top right corner (?).
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item
         href="/org.eclipse.jst.j2ee.doc.user/topics/cjpers.html"
         skip="true"
         title="Open the Java EE perspective">
      <description>
         When working with JAX-WS Web services, you should use the Java EE perspective. If you already have the Java EE perspective active, you may skip this step by clicking the <b>Click to Skip</b> button. If not, select <b>Window -&gt; Open Perspective -&gt; Other...</b> from the main menu and  choose <b>Java EE</b> in the resulting <b>Open Perspective</b> dialog box.
      </description>
      <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective(org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective.perspectiveId=org.eclipse.jst.j2ee.J2EEPerspective)"/>
   </item>
   <item
         dialog="true"
         href="/org.eclipse.jst.ws.cxf.doc.user/tasks/create_cxf_project.html"
         skip="true"
         title="Create a Dynamic Web Project">
      <description>
         Before creating a JAX-WS Web Service, we need a project to put it in. Perform the following steps to create an Dynamic Web Project.
<br/>
<br/>
Select <b>File -&gt; New -&gt; Project...</b> from the main menu, expand the <b>Web</b> category within the resulting <b>New Project</b> dialog box and choose <b>Dynamic Web Project</b>.
<br/>
<br/>
On the first page of the wizard enter a <b>Project name:</b>, select Apache Tomcat as the <b>Target runtime</b> and click <b>Finish</b>.
      </description>
      <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.newWizard(newWizardId=org.eclipse.jst.servlet.ui.project.facet.WebProjectWizard)"/>
   </item>
   <item
         href="/org.eclipse.jst.ws.cxf.doc.user/tasks/install_cxf_facet.html"
         skip="true"
         title="Enable JAX-WS Web service developement">
      <description>
         Enable a Dynamic Web Project for Apache CXF Web services development by right-clicking on the project and selecting <b>Properties</b>.
<br/>
<br/>
In the <b>Project Facets</b> page enable the <b>CXF 2.x Web Services</b> facet by selecting the check box and click <b>OK</b>.
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
